Autograph File, B: Guide.
Autograph File, B,
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s. to Aaron Burr; Sandy Hill, 17 Nov 1819., 1s.(3p.)
  *45M-181 (87) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s.to Aaron Burr; Washington, 26 Mar 1819., 1s.(3p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s.to Aaron Burr; Albany, 18 Jul 1821., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s.to James V. Henry; Albany, 17 Apr 1823., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s. to Caleb Lamson; [n.p.] 15 Aug 1855., 1s.(1p.)
  *42M-1955. From the estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Thomas Barbour and others, June 1942.
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s. to Thomas W. Olcott; Kinderhook, 28 Aug 1832., 1s.(2p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L. (3d person) to L. H. Smith; [n.p.] 27 Nov 1834., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. MS.D.s.; Albany, 1 Aug 1822., 1s.(4p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1795-1858. A.L.s.to John Canfield Spencer; New York, 18 Apr 1846., 1s.(2p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1818-1893. A. signature; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1818-1893. Autograph signature. Boston, Apr 1871., 1s.(1p.)
  *42M-1954. From the estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Thomas Barbour and others, June 1942.
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1818-1893. A.L.s.to Editor of the "Nation"; Lowell, 12 Nov 1860., 1s.(1p.) env.
  Enclosing 14-page printed part of "Popular Monthly" containing article "Election Day" by Louis Jay Lang.
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1818-1893. A. signature on fragment of MS.L.to Wendell Phillips; Boston [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1818-1893. MS.L.s.to Stephen Bradshaw Ives; Washington, 2 Apr 1874., 1s.(2p.)
- Butler, Caleb. A.L.s.to Messrs. Knowles; Locke; Groton, 9 Oct 1838., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Charles, 1750-1832. A.L.(3d person) to [ ] Hanes; [n.p.] 19 Jul [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
  Contains A.MS.s.note about the finding of the above by Edward Wigglesworth, 25 Dec 1833.
- Butler, Charles, 1750-1832. A.L.s.to [ ]; London, 3 May 1813., 1s.(2p.)
- Butler, Matthew Calbraith, 1836-1909. MS.L.s.to H. G. Gibson; Edgefield C.H.S.C., 22 Sep 1878., 1s.(2p.)
- Butler, Pierce, 1744-1822. A.L.s.to the Cashier, Bank of Pennsylvania; Philadelphia, 2 Jun 1796., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Pierce, 1744-1822. A.L.s.to E. Griffith; [n.p.] 1 Oct 1819., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, Pierce, 1744-1822. A.L.s. to [ ]; Philadelphia, 18 Dec 1808., 1s.(3p.)
- Butler, Robert Signature on a document giving an account of ship repairs in Charleston harbor. July 18, 1823.
- Butler, Samuel, 1835-1902. A.L.s. to [ ]; [London] 3 May 1893., 1s.(1p.)
  *47M-269. Gift of Earl Lealie Griggs, 8 May 1948.
- Butler, William Allen, 1825-1902. A.L.s.to A. J. Danton; [New York] 12 Feb 1894., 1s.(1p.)
- Butler, William Allen, 1825-1902. A.L.s.to George A. Shaw; New York, 15 Jan 1884., 1s.(1p.)
  Also signed portrait.
- Butt, George, 1741-1795. A.L.s.to Editor of Literary Gazette; Inner Temple, [n.d.]., 1s.(3p.)
- Butterfield, Carlos. A.signature; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Butterfield, Sir Herbert, 1900- [On historiography]. A.MS.; [n.p., 1950], 20s.(20p.)
  *51M-102. Gift of Sir Herbert Butterfield, 1951.
- Butterfield, Lyman Henry, 1909. Pugna porcorum. Verse translation (fragment) of Joannes Placentius, Pugna porcorum, with notes on the Oxford1768 edition. A.MS.; [n.p., n.d.]., 3s.(3p.)
  Removed from *85-25-43.
  Purchased with the Amy Lowell fund, 2 Dec 1982.
- Butterfield, W. MS.copy of subpoena to John Goodwin Locke; Boston, 24 Oct 1834., 1s.(1p.)
  Signed by W. Butterfield.
  Also original printed subpoena, not signed by W. Butterfield. 1s.(1p.)
- Butterworth, Hezekiah, 1839-1905. A.L.s.to B. W. Austin; Boston [n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
- Butterworth, Hezekiah, 1839-1905. A.L.s.to Edwin Percy Whipple; Boston, 15 [ ] 1881., 1s.(1p.)
- Butterworth, Hezekiah, 1839-1905. They who to others ... A.MS.s.; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Buttilliere [?] 3 MS.L.s. to Luiz de Vasconcellos e Sousa, 3. conde de Castello Melhor
  - Turin, 14 Aug 1677., 1s. (3p.)
  - Same, 2 Oct 1677., 1s. (4p.)
  - Same, 16 Oct 1677., 1s. (4p.)
- Byles, Mather, 1707-1788. A.MS.s.; [n.p.] 1741., 1s.(1p.)
  List of marriages performed by Mather Byles in 1741.
  *45M-181(88) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Bynner, E[ ] L[ ]. A.L.s. to Arlo Bates; Magnolia, 29 Aug [1916], 1s.(2p.)
- Bynner, Edwin Lassetter, 1842-1893. A.L.s. to [ ] Clements; Groton, 14 Nov [ ], 1s.(2p.)
  *47M-373 (17) Estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Alfred M. Tozzer,; Mrs. Thomas Barbour, and Miss Gertrude A. Thurston, June 1943.
- Bynner, Witter, 1881-1968. 2 letters to Gustave and Jane Baumann;1932-1958.
  *88M-37. Gift of Ann Baumann, 15 July 1988.
- Bynner, Witter, 1881-1968. 4 letters to Orton Loring Clark;1954-1959.
  Copies, with annotations.
  With 2 1954 letters.
  Copies of bMS Am 1891 (172).
- Bynner, Witter, 1881- A.L.s.to Henry Cole Quinby; [n.p., 24 Mar 1918], 1s.(2p.) card.
  *44WM-16. No source, Spring 1944.
- Bynner, Witter, 1881-1968. A.L.s. to William Roscoe Thayer; [Boston] 26 Sep 1907., 1s.(2p.) env.
- Byrne, James, 1857-1942. A.L.s. to "Dean" [ ]; [New York] 17 Oct 1926., 1s.(2p.)
  *47M-373 (18). Estate of Samuel Henshaw. Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Alfred M. Tozzer,; Mrs. Thomas Barbour, and Miss Gertrude A. Thurston, June 1943.
- Byron, Anne Isabella (Millbanke) Byron, baroness, 1792-1860. A.L.s.to [Augusta (Byron)] Leigh
  - Hanger Hill (?); 13 Jan 1830., 1s.(1p.)
  - On verso of A.L.s. Augusta (Byron) Leigh to Baroness Byron, 12 Jan 1830., 1s.(1p.)
- Byron, Anne Isabella (Millbanke) Byron, baroness, 1792-1860. A.L.s.to [Augusta (Byron) Leigh]; Brighton, 12 Apr 1857., 1s.(2p.)
- Byron, Anne Isabella (Millbanke) Byron, baroness, 1792-1860. A.L.s.to [Augusta (Byron) Leigh]; [n.p.,n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Byron, Anne Isabella (Millbanke) Byron, baroness, 1792-1860. A.L.s.to [ ] Colman; [London] [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Byron, Anne Isabella (Millbanke) Byron, baroness, 1792-1860. A.L.(3d person) to [ ] Wood; Fordhook, 4 Nov [n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
- Byron, George Gordon Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824. A.L.(unsigned) to [ ]; [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
  Written on verso of printed copy of poem, Lines written, on hearing that the Austrians had entered Naples.
  *45M-181 (89) Gift of James Freeman Clarke, Feb 1946.
- Byron, George Gordon Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824. A.L.(fragment, unsigned) to [William John Bankes]; [n.p., ca. 1807.], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. MS Eng 38*.
- Byron, George Gordon Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824. A.L.(signature wanting) to [Richard Belgrave] Hoppner; Venice, 7 Dec 1819., 1s.(3p.)
  A draft has been cut off, probably by recipient.
  *43M-129F. Gift of Dr Harris Kennedy, 26 Sept 1943.
- Byron, Lord Doc. Signed: Pass to theatre box. [London], 27 Jun 1815., 1p.
  Norton autographs, 15 July 1914.
- Byron, George Gordon Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824. A.L.(fragment) to Edward Noel Long; [Cambridge, 21? Nor 1807.], 1s.(2p.)
  *42M-635. Purchased with the Perkins fund from Elkin Mathews Ltd., 2 Apr 1943.
- Byron, George Gordon Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824. Memorie di versi scritti nel ano 1818. Dal signor Lor Bair in Venezia... MS. (copied by Battista, Byron's servant); [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(1p.)
  3 poems of Byron translated into Italian.
  *42M-499(24) Gift of Dr. Harris Kennedy, 26 Sept 1943.
- Byron, George Gordon Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824. A.L.s. to John Wilson Croker; [London] 13 Jul [1813], 1s. (3p.)
  *42M-1018. Received on exchange from Howard S. Mott, 20 June 1943.
- Byron, Lord George. Facsimile manuscript
  First page of the Manuscript of Byron's Sardanapalus.
- Bywater, Ingram, 1840-1914. [Bibliographical errors in modern editions of classical texts] A.MS.; [n.p., n.d.], 6s. (6p.)
  *67M-176. Removed from books belonging to W. A. Jackson, 1964.
- Bywater, Ingram, 1840-1914. A.L.s.to [Hermann Diels]; [London] 15 Jun 1908., 1s.(1p.)
  Removed from *61-1570.